CONTACT



+91 98798 81409



mitul.chhabhaya90@gmail.com



mitul90.github.io/porfolio.github.io



linkedin.com/in/mitul-chhabhaya

LANGUAGES

NextJs	
	85%
ReactJs	
	85%
ReactBootstrap	
	95%
Javascript	
	90%
HTML/CSS	
	98%
SCSS	
	95%
Bootstrap	
	100%
jQuery	
	80%
Chrome Extension	
	95%

SKILLS

Design to HTML

	100%
WordPress Front-end	
	95%
Shopify Front-end	
	95%
GIT	
	80%

MITUL

CHHABHAYA

Front-end Developer

About



I am a front-end web developer with 10+ years of experience has developed 100+ websites and helped multiple clients. Specialize in high-quality NextJs, ReactJs, ReactBootstrap, HTML, SCSS, CSS, JavaScript, and JQuery. Customizing WordPress, and Shopify themes, and experience in Chrome extension development.

Happy to help you build websites with optimized page speed and SEO-friendly.

Experience



JAN 2020 - PRESENT NAVINES Sr. Front-end Developer

APR 2019 - DEC 2019 Spinx Digital

Sr. Front-end Developer

AUG 2016 - APR 2019 Shreeji Web Technologies Pvt. Ltd.

Sr. Front-end Developer

SEP 2013 - AUG 2016 Nichetech Computer Solutions Pvt. Ltd.

TL / Sr. Web Designer

FEB 2013 – SEP 2013 Global Easy web Solution

Web Designer

Education



APRIL 2014 Saurashtra University M.Com

KK Parekh Commerce College – Amreli

Achievement



APR 2015 Certificate Of Appreciation
Nichetech Computer Solutions Pvt. Ltd

AUG 2014 Excellent Performer Of The Month

Nichetech Computer Solutions Pvt. Ltd

NOV 2013 Rising Star Of The Month

Nichetech Computer Solutions Pvt. Ltd

Certification



NOV 2012 Certificate In Web Design
Red & White Multimedia Education - Surat